What are some key difference between
creating content on Instagram compared to
YouTube that you've found?
Best rule for both, it's not about you.
Yeah.
It's never about you.
Fitness people do a vlog.
No one fucking cares.
Yeah.
They don't care. And for me,
I've accepted that now.
I'm a vessel of information.
It's always about them.
Mm-hmm.
Everything is about them.
Yeah.
So stop posting your fucking lunch,
stop posting your fucking workout, start
thinking about their problems
and help them, because if you
are subservient to
their needs, they will love you for it.
Mm-hmm.
The minute you make it about yourself,
which can happen when people get a big
following, they start thinking,
"I have a big following because I'm
great." When
the truth is,
you have a big following because you
helped a lot of people.
Yeah.
Even little things, right?
My thumbnails,
I was putting myself in it
when the video wasn't about me.
Mm-hmm.
I was like,
"Why the fuck have I just put my face..."
If you're talking about the iPhone
and you've got a big iPhone channel,
you can
believe it's the iPhone that's in the
picture.
Yeah.
Where some people are like...
Get your fucking face out of it.
They don't care about you